submit.biz 2006-06-14

# Search engine marketing and top search engine placement :: Submit.biz

Submit.biz and Worldwide Marketing strongly believes in protecting consumer privacy. This statement describes the privacy practices for the Worldwide-Marketing Web sites: 

If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, [ click here](http://webpromotion.supportdesk.co.uk/)

**1\. What information do we gather and track, and what do we do with it?**

  * About information gathered from your use of our site:  
Because we want to provide you with a compelling reason to visit our site on a repeat basis.    
The software on our server uses cookies to store certain types of information like, your password. We retrieve any information about your visit for our own use. Most web browsers allow you to stop receiving cookies if you want to, and you can do this yourself on your computer. (Please see your browser help or contact the software manufacturer for the instructions.)
  * Information gathered on registration: Our registration form may require you to give us contact and billing information (like your name, address and email) credit card details, if applicable, will be taken at a later date. Registration is free. We use information you provide on the registration form for accounting and contact purposes (for example, to respond to your queries or for other customer service issues or to issue VAT invoices).   
We may use your registration information to send you information about our company and our services. You may opt-out of receiving future mailings at any time; use the newsletter form, contact form or email us if you wish to be removed from any mailings. 
  * Information you supply us: Emails sent to us may be used for testimonial purposes on our site, but will be withdrawn immediately at your request. Just use the contact form or email us direct with your instructions. If you register to receive newsletters or other information from us by email, then we will use that email address to send you newsletters or information you have registered to receive. You may opt out of receiving future newsletters and/or other information you have registered to receive from us at any time; simply use the newsletter form, contact form or email us with your instructions. 

**2\. Sharing of the information**

We do not sell, share, trade or give away personal information about our customers other than as described in this policy. 

    * Companies in the Worldwide Marketing group, we may share data supplied by you (or collected about you) with our subsidiaries and other companies in our group, but only for the purposes described in this policy. 
    * Third parties Where you use our site to enter into a transaction or correspond with another company or person, we may provide information supplied by you (or collected about you) to that other party in order to facilitate the transaction or the correspondence, we only include your contact details, but do not give any payment details like credit cards etc as it is your responsibility to settle the items bought directly with the vendor. 

**Changes in our business**  
If all of the assets which we use to operate our business (or substantially all of them) are acquired by a third party, we may transfer personal data we then hold to that party. In the unlikely event that an insolvency practitioner (such as a liquidator) is appointed in respect of our business, that practitioner may sell, trade or rent personal data we then hold. 

**Overseas transfers**  
Due to the nature of our business and to enable us to offer you goods and services from around the world, your data may be transferred to any country in the world for the purposes described in this policy. 

**3\. Security**

We are committed to the security of customer information and we have security procedures in place to protect the loss, misuse or alteration of information under our control. Our online payments are taken directly by our bankers secure servers, so no payment information is entered into our server. If you do not have a secure browser or do not wish to send your credit card details over the web using a secure browser, you are welcome to open an account by fax, phone or letter.   
Additionally, we have security measures in place to protect our customer database and access to this database is restricted internally. However, it remains important for you to protect against unauthorised access to your account by keeping your password secret and exiting from our web site when you are not using it. 

**4\. Unsubscribe policy**

We provide you with the opportunity to unsubscribe from receiving communications from us, our group of companies and our partners at the time when we send out a mailing or you may unsubscribe from our mailing list on the web site/s using the newsletter form, contact form or email us with your instructions. 

**6\. Change or update your details**

We provide the following options for changing and updating information you previously provided to us:   

  * Contact us using the contact form or email us with your new details. 
  * Send a letter to our postal address:  
Dept. submit.biz  
Worldwide Marketing  
2 Barton Orchard  
Tipton St John  
Devon  
EX10 AN  
England. 
  * Call us on: (44) 0845 058 0561 - lo-call rate number  
Fax us on: (44) 0870 737 9182    
Hours of Business (GMT time zone)  
Mon - Fri: 9:30am till 5:30pm
  * We will make any amendments requested within approximately 10 working days of their receipt. 

**7\. Contacting Worldwide Marketing**

This web site is operated by:  
Worldwide Marketing  
2 Barton Orchard  
Tipton St John  
Devon  
EX10 AN  
England.  
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the practices of this site, or your dealings with our company, please do not hesitate to contact us using our contact form, email us or write to the above address, please include the web site address. You can also use this address if you wish to request from Worldwide-Marketing a copy of the personal data we hold about you or a description of that data. Please note that by English law we are entitled to charge you a small sum for providing this information. 

**8\. Links to third party sites**

This web site may contains links to other sites. We are not responsible for the privacy practices, or the content of these web sites. 

We reserve the right to add, delete or amend these terms and condition with immediate effect.
